In the last video we talked about the difference between static and dynamic
在上一个视频中，我们谈到了静电和Dynamic之间的区别
typing, and how one trend in static typing is towards increasingly expressive type
打字，以及静电打字的一个趋势是如何朝着表现力越来越强的类型发展
systems. In this lecture we're gonna talk about self type, which will give you a
系统。在这节课中，我们将讨论自我类型，这将给你一个
taste or what those more expressive type systems can look like. To begin with,
品味或那些更具表现力的文字系统看起来会是什么样子。首先，
let's motivate the problem that self types solves, by looking at a simple class
让我们通过查看一个简单的类来激发Self类型解决的问题
definition, so here we have class counts, and it has a single field I, which is an
定义，所以这里我们有类计数，它只有一个字段i，这是一个
integer initialized to zero, and it has one method increment. And essentially, the
整数初始化为零，并且它有一个方法增量。从本质上讲，
class count just increments a counter. So you, initially when you allocate a new
类计数只是递增计数器。所以你，最初当你分配一个新的
count object, the counter is zero, and then every time you call ink, the
对象，计数器为零，则每次调用手写输入时，
counter's value is increased by one. And notice that this can be thought of as a
计数器的值加一。请注意，这可以被认为是
base class that provides counter functionality, so whenever I wanted a
提供计数器功能的基类，因此每当我想要一个
counter for some specific purpose, I get to find a new sub-class and that, of
为了某个特定的目的，我可以找到一个新的子类，
count, and that sub-class would automatically inherit the inc-method,
计数器，子类将自动继承Inc-Method，
thereby allowing me to have counter without having to re-implement the code.
从而允许我在不必重新实现代码的情况下具有计数器。
In this case the code is very, very small, but in general you can imagine having a
在本例中，代码非常非常小，但通常您可以想象拥有一个
class that implements something tricky, or requiring a lot of code, and it's useful
实现一些棘手的东西或需要大量代码的类，它很有用
to be able to reuse that in sub-classes. Now consider a sub class account that we
以便能够在子类中重用它。现在考虑一个子类帐户，我们
might want to define called stock. Say we're implementing a warehouse accounting,
可能需要定义一下所谓的股票。假设我们正在实施仓库会计，
program and we want to keep track of the number of items that are in stock of
程序，并且我们希望跟踪库存项目的数量
certain different kinds. So we define a new class stock that inherits from count,
某些不同的种类。因此我们定义了一个新类Stock，它继承自Count，
and now we'll have a new field in here to make this, Object that's classed different
现在，我们在这里将有一个新字段来使其分类为不同的对象
from its parent will just have a name that, corresponds to the name of the, the
将只有一个名称，该名称对应于
item that's in stock. And now, down here, we can actually use this. We can decla-,
有库存的物品。现在，在这里，我们实际上可以用这个。我们可以取消-，
allocate a new stock object, we create a new object. We increment it To indicate
分配一个新的股票对象，我们就创建一个新的对象。我们递增它以表示
that we have one thing in stock And then we assign it to some variable that we've
我们有一个库存，然后我们把它赋给某个变量
declared of typed stock And then later on we can use this A object as we like. Now,
声明了类型化的股票，然后我们可以随意使用这个A对象。现在,
the problem is that this code actually will not type-check. There is a type error
问题是这段代码实际上不会进行类型检查。存在类型错误
in this code. And why is that? Well, let's think about it for a minute. So, what is
在此代码中。为什么会这样呢？嗯，让我们考虑一下。那么，什么是
the signature of inc? So inc, remember, was declared to return things of type
是Inc.的签名吗？因此，请记住，Inc.被声明为返回类型为
count. Right, and when the inc method is inherited by the stock class this
伯爵。对，当STOCK类继承Inc方法时，
signature doesn't change, it still returns things of type count. So here we have a
签名不变，它仍然返回COUNT类型的内容。所以我们这里有一个
new stock object we call the increment method But the type of this whole thing is
New Stock对象，我们调用Increment方法，但整个对象的类型是
a count and then we try to assign that to a stock, but that doesn't work because
然后我们尝试将其赋给一只股票，但这不起作用，因为
count. Is not a subtype of stock, a variable of type stock can't hold a value
伯爵。不是STOCK的子类型，类型为STOCK的变量不能保存值
of type count and so the type system will report an error right here at the
，因此类型系统将在此处的
assignment statement. And you can see that this is actually a serious problem,
赋值语句。你可以看到这实际上是一个严重的问题，
because it has made the inheritance of the increment method pretty useless. I can
因为它使增量方法的继承变得非常无用。我可以的
define new sub-classes of stock, but I can never use the increment method on them, at
定义新的股票子类，但我永远不能对它们使用增量方法，在
least not without getting back something of the parent type. And so it's not as,
至少在没有拿回一些父类的东西的情况下是这样的。所以这不像，
the inheritance of the incremental method is not as useful as one might have hoped.
增量方法的继承并不像人们希望的那样有用。
So just to review, new stock, the, the incremented new stock, will have dynamic
所以我再回顾一下，新股，这个，增量的新股，会有动态的
type stock. That'll actually be a stock object that is returned, okay. So don't
键入STOCK。这实际上是一个返回的股票对象，好的。所以不要
get confused here. This is the dynamic type I'm talking about. So when we,
在这里搞糊涂吧。这就是我所说的动态类型。所以当我们，
allocate the new stock object, and then we call the increment method, remember the
分配新的股票对象，然后我们调用增量方法，记住
increment method returns self so the increment method was implemented something
Increment方法返回self，因此Increment方法实现了一些
like this. Leave out the types but it was I gets I + one and it returned the self
像这样。去掉类型，但它是我得到了I+1，它返回了自我
object alright, so it's definitely returning whatever object is passed in
对象，所以它绝对会返回传入的任何对象
here at the dispatch point so it's returning something of dynamic type stock.
这里是分派点，所以它返回一些动态类型的股票。
And, so this program will actually run if we didn't have type-checking. If we
所以，如果我们没有进行类型检查，这个程序实际上会运行。如果我们
actually run this and it would work just fine. This would produce a dynamic stock
实际运行这个程序，它会工作得很好。这将产生一个充满活力的股票
object and would store it into the stock variable. But it's not well typed because
对象，并将其存储到STOCK变量中。但它的打字不是很好，因为
the ty pe checker loses track of the fact that this is a stock object. All it knows
类型检查器会忘记这是库存对象这一事实。它所知道的一切
is that increment is declared to have return type count, and, which is certainly
增量被声明为具有返回类型COUNT，这肯定是
correct because every stock object is also a count object, it's just not useful in
正确，因为每个股票对象也是一个计数对象，只是在
the context of this piece of code. And so the type checker loses information. Which
这段代码的上下文。因此类型检查器会丢失信息。哪一个
make it not very pleasant to try to put the increment method in the count class to
尝试将Count类中的增量方法放到
begin with. So to solve this problem, we're going to look at extending the type
首先。为了解决这个问题，我们将考虑扩展类型
system. The insight is going to be that the increment method returns self. In this
系统。我们的洞察力将是，增量方法返回Self。在这里面
case, the increment method actually returns the self object, and therefore the
情况下，增量方法实际上返回Self对象，因此
return value is going to have the same type as self. Whatever self happens to be,
返回值将与self具有相同的类型。不管自己是什么样子，
which could be count or it could be any sub-type of count. So the self object only
其可以是计数，也可以是计数的任何子类型。所以只有Self对象
has to be dynamically something that holds a value that's a sub-type of the declared
必须是动态保存一个值的东西，该值是声明的
type of the self parameter, and so it could be any one of the sub-types in this
类型，因此它可以是此参数中的任意子类型
case of the count class. And to do this we're actually gonna have to introduce a
伯爵类的案例。要做到这一点，我们实际上必须引入一个
new key word called self type, that is gonna be used as the return of the type of
名为self type的新关键字，它将用作
the return value of such functions. And we're gonna have to modify our typing
此类函数的返回值。我们将不得不修改我们的打字方式
rules to handle this new kind of type. So the idea behind self type is it's going to
处理这种新类型的规则。所以自我类型背后的想法是它将会
allow the type to change, when inc is inherited, or allow us to reason about how
允许在继承Inc.时更改类型，或者允许我们对如何更改类型进行推理
the actual return type dynamically of increment method changes when the
时，增量方法的实际返回类型会动态更改
increment method is inherited. So we change the declaration of inc to read as
Increment方法是继承的。因此，我们将Inc的声明更改为
follows. We've declared the return type now to be self type, meaning the return
下面是。我们现在已经将返回类型声明为self类型，这意味着返回
value Of the increment method has whatever type. Is the type of the original self
增量方法的值可以是任何类型。是原始自我的类型
parameter? And when we do that now we can see. That it's possible. We don't, we
参数？当我们这样做的时候，我们现在可以看到。这是可能的。我们没有，我们
haven't said how we do it, but you should be able to see that it intuitively makes
我没有说我们是怎么做的，但你应该能直观地看到
sense that we could prove facts of the following forms. So when the self
感觉我们可以证明以下形式的事实。所以当自我
parameter has the type count, remember that the thing we dispatch to, the thing
参数具有类型COUNT，请记住我们调度到的对象
we call inc on, is the self para meter. So when we dispatch to account object, we get
我们调用Inc on，是自我参数。因此，当我们调度到Account对象时，我们会得到
something back of type count. And we call, when we, when we dispatch on a stock
后面的文字很重要。当我们，当我们派发库存的时候，我们会打电话
object, when we call increment on a stock object, well, what's the type of self? The
对象，当我们在股票对象上调用增量时，那么，自我的类型是什么呢？这个
type is stock, and we get back something of type stock. And now the program that we
类型是STOCK，我们得到的是STOCK类型的东西。现在我们的节目是
had before with this one change is well typed and would be accepted by the Cool
以前有过这样的更改，类型很好，会被Cool接受
type system. Now it's very important to remember that self type is not a dynamic
键入system。现在非常重要的是要记住，自我类型不是动态的
type it is very much a static type and part of the static type system. It's also
类型它很大程度上是一个静电类型，是静电类型系统的一部分。它也是
important to realize that self type is not a class name. So unlike all the other
重要的是要认识到，self类型不是类名。所以不像所有其他的
static types in cool, it is not a name of a class, it's its own special thing and
静电打字很酷，它不是一个类名，它是它自己特别的东西
we'll say more about exactly what it is in future videos, but the purpose of self
我们将在未来的视频中更多地讲述它到底是什么，但自我的目的
type as we've seen is to enable to type checker to accept more correct programs
我们所看到的类型是启用类型检查器来接受更多正确的程序
and effectively. What self type does is to increase the expressive power of the type system.
而且非常有效。自我类型所做的就是增加类型系统的表现力。